The only thing more dangerous than the front lines was the fight to get there.
Greyhound is a war, action, drama film directed by Aaron Schneider.
A first-time captain leads a convoy of allied ships carrying thousands of soldiers
across the treacherous waters of the "Black Pit" to the front lines of WWII.
With no air cover protection for 5 days, the captain and his convoy must battle the
surrounding enemy Nazi U-boats in order to give the allies a chance to win the war.
Commander Krause, played by Tom Hanks.
Charlie Cole, played by Stephen Graham.
Cleveland, played by Rob Morgan.
Talker #1, played by Josh Wiggins.
Lt. Watson, played by Tom Brittney.
Evelyn, played by Elisabeth Shue.
Greyhound is a 2020 American war film directed by Aaron Schneider and
starring Tom Hanks, who also wrote the screenplay.
The film is based on the 1955 novel The Good Shepherd by C.
Forester, and follows a US Navy commander on his first assignment commanding a multi-national escort
destroyer group of four, defending an Allied convoy from U-boats during the Battle of the Atlantic.
The film also stars Stephen Graham, Rob Morgan, and Elisabeth Shue.
Greyhound was initially scheduled for theatrical release in the United
States on June 12, 2020, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The release was delayed indefinitely and then canceled because of
widespread disruption and shutdowns from the COVID-19 pandemic.
Sony sold the distribution rights to Apple TV+, which
released the film digitally on July 10, 2020.
It received positive reviews from critics, with praise for the action
sequences and effective use of its 90-minute runtime.
At the 93rd Academy Awards, the film earned a nomination for Best Sound.
The film explores themes of submarine, allies, atlantic
ocean, world war ii, based on true story.
The tone is emotional and intense.